Guide to the United Nations Oral History Project Interview Transcripts and Tapes
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Inventory
  - Tapes
    - Meguid, Ahmed Esmat Abdel, audiocassette (Box 165)
    - Millard, Guy, 2 audiocassettes (Box 166–167)
    - Montaño, Jorge, 2 audiocassettes (Box 168–169)
    - Mudge, Dirk, audiocassette (Box 170)
    - Murray, Geoffrey, 2 audiocassettes (Box 171–172)
    - Myint-U, Thant, audiocassette (Box 173)
    - Nassif, Ramses, 3 audiocassettes, 1998 March 9, undated (Box 174–175, Box 250)
    - Nusseibeh, Hazem, audiocassette (Box 176)
    - Ortega, Humberto
      - Original, 1 (Box 177)
      - Corrected copy of original, audiocassette (Box 178)
    - Ortiz de Rozas, Carlos, audiocassette (Box 179)
    - Otunnu, Olara, audiocassette (Box 180)
    - Pachachi, Adnan, audiocassette (Box 181)
      - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 181U)
    - Parsons, Anthony, 2 audiocassettes (Box 182–183)
    - Pell, Claiborne, audiocassette (Box 184)
    - Pettersen, Helmer, 1 (Box 253)
    - Picco, Giandomenico, audiocassette (Box 185)
    - Pickering, Thomas, audiocassette (Box 186)
    - Pineau, M. Christian, 2 audiocassettes (Box 187–188)
    - Rafael, Gideon, 2 audiocassettes (Box 189–190)
    - Rangel, Beatrice, 2 audiocassettes (Box 191–192)
    - Richardson, Elliot, audiocassette (Box 193)
    - Rikhye, Indar Jit, 2 audiocassettes (Box 194–195)
    - Ritter, Scott, 2 audiocassettes (Box 196–197)
    - Ros, Enrique, 2 audiocassettes (Box 198–199)
    - Roschin, Alexei, 2 audiocassettes (Box 200–201)
    - Rosenne, Shabtai, 4 audiocassettes (Box 202–205)
    - Sáenz, Miguel, audiocassette (Box 206)
    - Samayoa, Salvador, audiocassette (Box 207)
    - Sanderson, John, 2 audiocassettes (Box 208–209)
    - Shejavali, Selma, 2 audiocassettes (Box 210–211)
    - Sherry, George, 3 audiocassettes (Box 212–214)
    - Shihabi, Samir, audiocassette (Box 215)
    - Sills, Joe (Box 251)
    - Sisco, Joseph, audiocassette (Box 216)
    - Smidovich, Nikita, 2 audiocassettes (Box 217–218)
    - Sommerfelt, Soren Christian, audiocassette (Box 219)
    - Steiner, Ismat, audiocassette (Box 220)
    - Stephanides, Joseph, audiocassette (Box 221)
    - Tello, Manuel and Gustavo Albin, audiocassette (Box 222)
    - Tjitendero, Mosé, 2 audiocassettes (Box 223–224)
    - Tomeh, George, 2 audiocassettes (Box 225–226)
    - Tueni, Ghasson, 2 audiocassettes (Box 227–228)
    - Van Bellinghen, Jean Paul, 3 audiocassettes (Box 229–231)
    - Vargas, Maurici, audiocassette (Box 232)
    - Vendrell, Francesco, 1 (Box 254)
    - Verheul, Adriaan, audiocassette (Box 233)
    - Watson, Alexander, 2 audiocassettes (Box 234–235)
    - Williams, Michael, audiocassette (Box 236)
    - Zamora, Ruben, audiocassette (Box 237)
    - Zelaya, Marina, audiocassette (Box 238)